<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<experiment_text language="English">
  <map name="default">
    <item key="Instructions">In this experiment, we are interested in how well you can judge the concrete/abstractness of a word.

A series of words will be spoken. Your task is to judge whether each word is CONCRETE or Abstract. 

This experiment will start by familiarizing you with some concrete and abstract words first, the test session. 

Only during the test session will you be required you to make responses.

Please refrain from counting or foot-tapping. It is very important to remember duration by heart.

Press SPACE to begin listening to sample concrete and abstract words.</item>
    <item key="Concrete Caption">The word was: CONCRETE.</item>
    <item key="Abstract Caption">The word was: ABSTRACT.</item>
<item key="End Study Caption"> There are no more sample concrete and abstract words.</item>

    <item key="Response Prompt Caption SHORT RIGHT LONG LEFT">Squeeze the handle if you think the word is an abstract word.

Squeeze [RIGHT] handle if it is closer to the SHORT target duration.

Press SPACE to begin practice session when you are ready.</item>
<item key="Response Prompt Caption LONG RIGHT SHORT LEFT">Squeeze [RIGHT] handle if you think the duration of this tone is closer to the LONG target duration.

Squeeze [LEFT] handle if it is closer to the SHORT target duration.

Press SPACE to begin practice session when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Feedback correct Caption">Correct!</item>
    <item key="Feedback wrong Caption">Incorrect!</item>
    <item key="Feedback slow Caption">Too slow!</item>
<item key="Feedback Long">The sound was LONG</item>
<item key="Feedback Short">The sound was SHORT</item>
    <item key="No Instructions Caption">Press SPACE to begin the next part.</item>
    

    <item key="Rest Screen Caption">Click the left mouse button to begin when you are ready to move on to the next part.</item>
    <item key="Progress Bar Caption">Progress:</item>
    <item key="Practice Caption">You will start by doing a few examples for practice.
If you fail to get the target durations correct, you will repeat this practice.</item>
    <item key="Practice Complete Caption">You have completed the practice.
	
 
Click SPACE to start the actual experiment.

Please try your best to stay attentative and do your best!</item>
<item key="Practice Repeat Caption">You must repeat the practice to contiune.</item>
<item key="Practice Fail Caption">Sorry, you are required to repeat this practice until you are ready to start the experiment. Please try harder this time!

Click SPACE to practice again.

</item>
    <item key="Completion Screen Caption">You have finished the experiment. Thank you very much for participating! Please inform the experimenter.</item>
    <item key="Block Complete Caption">In this block, you have correctly identified [BLOCK_STATS] of the target durations.

You have completed [BLOCK_NUMBER] block(s). 

There are [TOTAL_BLOCKS] blocks in the experiment. 

Press SPACE to move on.</item>
    <item key="Next Screen Caption">Press SPACE to continue.</item>
    <item key="Multi-Screen Start Experiment Caption">Press SPACE to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Start Experiment Caption">Press SPACE to start the experiment when you are ready.</item>
    <item key="Word Wrap Mode">Word</item>
  </map>
</experiment_text>